# Filip Lee

# Kockendal

Applied Information Technology Student



### CONTACT



Gothenburg, Sweden



(+46) 70 302 53 46



filip.kockendal@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

Hardworking and passionate student aiming at gaining experience and knowledge in the design and technology field. Through practical experience in interaction design, data visualization, and web development, I have developed a unique perspective on how to create intuitive and visually appealing digital experiences. With a focus on innovation and user-centered design, I am excited to both learn and bring my skills to new projects and challenges.

### **SKILLS**

#### TECHNICAL

- Figma
- · Adobe XD
- Photoshop
- · HTML/CSS
- Python
- · Power BI
- Microsoft Office
- · Google Suite

#### LANGUAGES

- Swedish Mother tongue
- · Enalish Fluent
- · Chinese Fluent

### **EXPERIENCE**

O SHOP ASSISTANT | JUN. 2020 - PRESENT

#### FINE LITTLE DAY

Working part-time in a lifestyle design company overseeing store operations

- Responsible for in-store sales, customer service and product display
- Packing and preparing online orders
- Collecting customer feedback and analysing customer behaviour

## ENGINEERING/PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT ADMIN | JUN. 2022 - AUG. 2022

#### VOLVO BUSES

Developed two tools to facilitate work for the employees at the company as a summer worker

- · A tool to visualize data
- · A tool to manage the project network between different teams

### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN APPLIED INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

> University of Gothenburg Cognitive Science 2020 - 2023

O HIGH SCHOOL
DIPLOMA IN
TECHNOLOGY

Aranäsgymnasiet Technical Science 2017 - 2019

# POSTMAN | SEP. 2019 - JAN. 2020; APR - JUN. 2020 POSTNORD

Worked full time as a postman

- · Sorted and delivered mail and packages
- · Categorised incoming parcels
- Organised packet distribution

# RESTAURANT ASSISTANT | APR - SEP. 2019; MAY - AUG. 2021

#### LISEBERG

Summer job at the restaurant Skeppsmagasinet in an amusement park

- · Worked at the cash register
- · Served drinks at the bar
- · Prepared food and washed dishes